unitedcountry.com 2013-05-03

# United Country Real Estate - Privacy Statement

  |     
---|---  
  
At United Country Real Estate (“United Country”) we are fully committed to the protection and security of the information provided to us by you, our clients, and others who use our Web site. We want you to be comfortable and confident about your privacy, so you can enjoy participating in our online offerings and so that we can  
better serve your needs.  

Our Privacy Statement discloses what you will want to know about our approach to privacy and how your   
personal information is collected and used. Your use of our Web site constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Statement and your consent to the practices it describes.

** What information we collect:**

Generally speaking, our Web site is informational. Your “personally identifiable information”, that is, information about you as an individual which would permit someone to contact you, is only requested in order for us to send you information such as our catalog, free bulletins and reports, to enable us to search for real estate properties meeting your search criteria, or to begin the process of listing your property for sale. We do not collect any personally identifiable information unless you voluntarily provide it.

As is the case when you visit most Web sites, to administer our site, your visit triggers the automatic logging   
of certain anonymous information about your computer system such as the type of browser you use, the server  
name and your “IP” (Internet Protocol) address. (When your web browser or email application requests a web   
page or email from another computer using the Internet, it automatically gives that computer your computer’s “address” so it knows where it should send the information. This is called your computer’s “IP address.”)   
This anonymous information does not contain any personally identifiable information about you.

| 

---|---  
  
**   
We protect your information:**

We protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information by using industry-recognized security safeguards such as firewalls, coupled with carefully developed security procedures to protect your information from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration.

Our employees are trained and required to safeguard your information and, using physical, electronic and procedural safeguards, we restrict access to personal information to those employees and agents for business purposes only. Additionally, we use internal and external resources to frequently review the adequacy of our security procedures. You need to know, however, that due to the open communication nature of the Internet we cannot guarantee   
that communication between you and us, and between us and you, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties nor can we be responsible for information stolen from our servers by information harvesting software which may have the ability to scrape data.

** We tell you how we intend to use your information:**

When we ask you for information, we tell you, or it will be clear, what we need to fulfill your request and how we use it.

** We do not sell or rent your personal information:**

Aside from our own real estate affiliates, we do not share your personal information with third parties for promotional use without your consent.   
You control what marketing information you receive from us.

We may, however, have to disclose, transfer, sell or assign your information obtained through this Web site, or otherwise in our possession, to a third   
party as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of United Country. We may also have to make information obtained through this Web site, or otherwise in our possession, available to law enforcement personnel and agencies when requested to do so or as required by law.

** We want to only provide you information you want:**

At any time, you can let us know whether or not you want to continue to receive information from us about our products or services or updated information about properties. If you do not wish to receive such material, you can specify your preference by emailing us at  [_ privacy@unitedcountry.com_](mailto:privacy@unitedcountry.com) You will also need to make this preference known to any particular United Country Team Member from whom you have received information about properties. 

** Cookie Technology:**

Cookie technology is employed on certain pages when you access our site at user’s option. The purpose of cookies is to better serve our users. In case   
you did not know, “cookies” are small text files sent by Web servers to be stored on the drive of Web site users. These files often contain personalization settings or unique identifiers, to keep track of your information and to help us understand the movements of users within and between Web sites.

** You can change your Information:**

You can update or correct your contact information by contacting United Country customer service   
at  [_ privacy@unitedcountry.com_](mailto:privacy@unitedcountry.com) _._

** Privacy Statement Changes:**

We reserve the right to change or amend our Privacy Statement to address new issues of privacy and information security and to reflect changes to   
our Web site or business practices. Any new changes and/or amendments will be noted on our Home Page and will always be posted in this section of the United Country Web site.

** Questions about our Privacy and Information Security Practices? **

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or procedures, please feel free to email us at  [_ privacy@unitedcountry.com_](mailto:privacy@unitedcountry.com). We care.
